couponshack.com 2006-12-20

# Coupon Shack: Privacy Policy

|  |   
---  

 Art & Crafts   
 Baby Goods   
 Books & Magazines   
 Business & Industrial   
 Cameras & Photo   
 Clothing, Shoes, Etc.   
 Computers & Electronics   
 Food & Beverage   
 Health & Beauty   
 Home & Garden   
 Jewelry & Watches   
 Money & Finance   
 Music & Movies   
 Pets   
 Sports   
 Tools & Automotive   
 Toys & Hobbies   
 Travel   
 Everything Else   
|   
---  
   
**Our Privacy Policy**

* * *

We are fully committed to the quality of our coupons as well as your coupon shopping experience. Our privacy policy is detailed below so that you have a better understanding of how we collect information and what the information is used for. We assure you that your personal information is kept safe and secure with our encryption technology and that the information is only intended to give you a better shopping experience by helping you to make more informed decisions before making your purchase. 

**What Information Do We Collect?**

* * *

When you visit our site you have the option to login/register and account. Please note that this is not required at all, but by doing so enhances your coupon shopping experience. The only required information we collect during registration is email address, username, and password (which is encrypted). The rest of the information during registration is optional. None of this information will ever be sold or traded with any outside party. 

**No Use of Our Site by Persons Under 13**

* * *

This site is not recommended for use by children under the age of 13 and registration is prohibited for anyone under the age of 13. See [www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy](http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy) for further details. 

**Cookies**

* * *

Our site does use tracking technology called "cookies" to collect information some information about how our site is used so that we may continually improve your shopping experience. This information may include the date and time of your visit, the pages viewed, or the sites visited just before and just after our site. No personal information or any identifying information is collected at all so that you will remain anonymous. You do have the option to turn off cookies should you not wish to share any information by adjusting your web browser settings. 

**What is a Cookie?**

* * *

A small text file of information that certain Web sites attach to a user's hard drive while the user is browsing the Web site. A Cookie can contain information such as user ID, user preferences, archive shopping cart information, etc. Cookies can contain Personally Identifiable Information (as defined below). 

**Governmental Requests**

* * *

We do not share or disclose any personal information of any visitors to CouponShack, but if required, we reserve the right to report any information collected to any legal authority. 

* Use of the CouponShack.com site indicates your knowledge and acceptance of this privacy policy.
